A Guide to the Dottie Schick Collection of Political Memorabilia, 1926-2004 (bulk 1968-2002)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Campaign buttons, 1937-2004., Extent: 21 boxes. (Box 25-45)
  This series includes campaign buttons for various national elections (President, Vice President, U.S. Congress), state elections (Attorney General, Governor, Lieutenant Governor, Sheriff, Supervisor, Virginia House of Delegates), and campaigns for Democratic National Convention Delegates. Also included are political statement, general Democratic Party, and various social organization buttons. Included are buttons for the campaigns of: Dick Bagley, Joe Biden, Leslie Byrne, Jimmy Carter, William Clinton, Howard Dean, Michael Dukakis, Dwight D. Eisenhower, Joe Fisher, John Glenn, Al Gore, Herb Harris, Gary Hart, Henry Howell, Hubert Humphrey, Lee Iacocca, Lyndon B. Johnson, John F. Kennedy, George McGovern (and Shriver), John Melnick, Andrew Miller, Harold Miller, Johun Milliken, Jim Moran, Walter Mondale (and Ferraro), Buck Morton, Richard Nixon, Nancy Pelosi, Rufus Phillips, Owen Pickett, J. Sargeant Reynolds, Charles Robb, Franklin D. Roosevelt, Terry Sanford, Dottie Schick, Paul Simon, Mary Sue Terry, Harry F. Truman, Bob Wallenberg, Mark Warner, Douglas Wilder, Carrington Williams, and Lynn Yeakel, among others.
  Of note are the inaugurations buttons/ribbons for Franklin D. Roosevelt, Harry F. Truman, Dwight Eisenhower, John F. Kennedy, Lyndon B. Johnson, and Jimmy Carter. Also include is a button for the transatlantic flight of Charles Lindbergh, New York to Paris. Most of the buttons are arranged alphabetically, although a large sash is included which contains a number of the more visually interesting buttons. (Box 45)
  Arranged alphabetically by candidates last name, with miscellaneous buttons arranged to the rear.
  - A-B. (Box 25)
  - B-E. (Box 26)
  - Carter, Jimmy. (Box 27)
  - Clinton, William J. (Box 28)
  - Dukakis, Michael. (Box 29)
  - F-G. (Box 30)
  - G-H. (Box 31)
  - H-L. (Box 32)
  - Mc-Mi. (Box 33)
  - Mi-Mo. (Box 34)
  - Mondale, Walter. (Box 35)
  - Mo-Ri. (Box 36)
  - Ro. (Box 37)
  - Ro-S. (Box 38)
  - T-W. (Box 39)
  - W-Z. (Box 40)
  - Political statements. (Box 41)
  - Democratic National Committee, Virginia. (Box 42)
  - Democratic National Committee. (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 44)
  - Various buttons on a sash. (Box 45)
- Series III: Artifacts, 1963-2002., Extent: 6 boxes. (Box 46-51)
  This series includes a variety of Democratic party artifacts collected by Dottie Schick. Included are license plates, stuffed animals (donkeys), commemorative coins for Presidents Clinton, Johnson, and Kennedy, convention paperweights, pens, saxophone lapel pin, and campaign cups and hats. Included are various plaques, including one with a piece of carpet from the Watergate Offices of the Democratic National Headquarters, 1972. Also included is a delegate convention package box from New York 1992.
- Series IV: Bumper stickers, ca. 1970-2000., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 52-58)
  This series includes bumper stickers for various Democratic candidates.
  Arranged alphabetically by candidates last name, with miscellaneous bumper stickers and name tags arranged to the rear.
  - A-G. (Box 52)
  - A-G. (Box 53)
  - H-M. (Box 54)
  - N-R. (Box 55)
  - S-Z. (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 57)
  - Name tags. (Box 58)
- Series V: Clippings, 1976-1992., Extent: 1 box. (Box 59)
  This series includes loose newspaper clippings on the various Democratic conventions and inaugurations.
- Series VI: Oversize, ca. 1970-2000., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 60-62)
  This series includes oversize certificates, invitations, photographs, and posters.
- Series VII: Scrapbooks, 1968-1992., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 63-65)
  This series includes scrapbooks for the 1968-1969 and 1981 national and state conventions; photographic scrapbook for the Harold O. Miller campaign 1969-1970; and a scrapbook for the 1992 election of President William Clinton, including photographs of Clinton at the Mason District Annual Crab Feast with Dottie Schick.